Guide to the Julius Bernstein Papers WAG.116
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: Subject Files, 1920-1984
  - Boston Red Sox: Discrimination Charges, 1959 (Box 4A, Folder 15)
  - Boston Teachers Union, undated (Box 4A, Folder 16)
  - Boston University Protests, 1968 (Box 4A, Folder 17)
  - Boycott: Boston, 1976 (Box 4A, Folder 18)
  - Brandeis University: Epic, 1961 (Box 4A, Folder 19)
  - Brandeis University: Lasker Fellowship, 1963 (Box 4A, Folder 20)
  - Brandeis University: Organizing, 1976-1977 (Box 4A, Folder 21)
  - Brandeis University: Socialist Club, 1961 (Box 4A, Folder 22)
  - Breira, 1976-1977 (Box 4A, Folder 23)
  - Brenner, Leon: Survey on Attitudes toward Judaism, 1959 (Box 4A, Folder 24)
  - Brooke, E., 1963 (Box 4A, Folder 25)
  - Brookline, 1968 (Box 4A, Folder 26)
  - Brookline Community Forum (JLC & Workmen's Circle), 1957-1965 (Box 4A, Folder 27)
  - Brookline Community Forum (JLC & Workmen's Circle), 1967 (Box 4A, Folder 28)
  - Buckley, William F., 1955-1966 (Box 4A, Folder 29)
  - Budenz, Louis, 1954 (Box 4A, Folder 30)
  - Burden of Truth (United Steel Workers), undated (Box 4A, Folder 31)
  - Cain, Harry, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - California State Federation of Labor, 1952-1953 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Cambridge Referendum, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Cambridge, MA: Affirmative Action Program, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Cannibal Cookbook, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Cape Verde: Harvard Students Support, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Capital Punishment, 1958-1967 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Carter, Jimmy: General, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Cases/Complaints: Discrimination, Anti-Semitism, etc., 1951-1960 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Catholic Church, 1955-1977 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Catholic Church and Labor, 1951, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Catholic Council on Civil Liberties, 1961-1962 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Catholic-Jewish Relations, 1963-1965, 1969, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Catholic Interracial Council of Boston, 1953-1969 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Cawley, Representative Robert L.: Constituents' Questionnaire, undated (Box 5, Folder 14a)
  - Censorship, 1957-1966 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Center for Dispute Settlement, 1964-1975 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Charter Reform: Boston, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Children and Prejudice, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Children's Campaign, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Chomsky, W.: Obituary, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 19a)
  - Christian Citizen's Committee, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Church and State, 1954-1963 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - C.I.A. (Fred Cook), 1961 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Circuit Riders, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Citizen's Anti-Communist Committee of Connecticut, 1961, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Citizens' Council (Boston), 1966 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Citizens Foreign Aid Committee, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Citizens Housing and Planning Association, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 26a)
  - Citizens for Human Rights, 1963-1970 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Citizens for McCarthy, 1954-1956 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Citizens for Participation in Political Action, 1975-1977 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Citizens for Participation in Political Action: Newsletter, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 29a)
  - Citizens Housing and Planning Association, undated (Box 5, Folder 29b)
  - City Missionary Society: Julius Bernstein Address, etc, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 29c)
  - Citywide Coordinating Council, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Citywide Coordinating Council: Boston H.S. Monitors' Reports, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Citywide Coordinating Council: Schools I, 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Citywide Coordinating Council: Schools II, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Citywide Coordinating Council: Schools III, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Citywide Coordinating Council: Schools IV, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Citywide Coordinating Council: Schools, Jan 1976-Apr 1976 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Citywide Coordinating Council: Schools, May 1976 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Citywide Coordinating Council: Schools, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Civic Unity Committees, 1954-1962 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Civil Liberties, 1950s-1970s (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Civil Liberties and Labor, 1954-1960 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Civil Liberties: Search and Seizure, 1961-1968 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Civil Liberties Union of Massachusetts, 1951-1975 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Civil Liberties Union of Massachusetts: Newsletters, 1958-1974 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Civil Rights: Black Power Split, 1962-1967 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Civil Rights: Black-White Split, 1961-1963 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Civil Rights: Boston, 1955-1970 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Civil Rights: Connecticut, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Civil Rights: Election, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Civil Rights: General, 1950s, 1960s (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Civil Rights: Labor Resolutions, 1954-1960 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Civil Rights: Legislation, 1953-1958 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Civil Rights: Legislation, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Civil Rights: Legislation, 1962-1964 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Civil Rights: National Legislation, 1955-1956 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Civil Rights: New England, 1957, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Civil Rights: Riots, 1964-1966 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Civil Rights Bills, 1959-1960 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Civil Rights Committee of the Massachusetts Labor Council, 1957-1962 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Civil Rights Committee of the Massachusetts Labor Council, 1963-1967 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Civil Rights Rally (Madison Square Garden), May 24, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Civil Rights Week, Jan 1949-Sep 1949 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Civil Rights Week, Oct 1949-Dec 1949 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Civil Rights Week, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Civil Rights Week, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Civil Rights Week, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Civil Rights Week, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Civil Rights Week, 1954 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Civil Rights Week, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Civil Rights Week, 1957 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Civil Rights Week, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Civil Rights Week, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Civil Rights Week, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Civil Service Reform: Governor's Council on Public Employment of the Disadvantaged, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Civil Service Reform: Governor's Council on Public Employment of the Disadvantaged, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 34a)
  - Clergy and Laymen Concerned about Vietnam, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Coalition, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Coalition of Black Trade Unionists, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Coalition of Labor Union Women, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Coalition to Fight Political Repression (re: Black Panthers), 1970 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Coffey, James F., 1955 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Commission on the Cities: Report, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Committee for American Freedom, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Committee of One Million, 1965-1966 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Communism: Jewish Labor Committee vs., 1953-1954 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Communism: Massachusetts Commission on, 1950s (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Communism: Massachusetts Commission on, 1950s (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Communism: Massachusetts Commission on: Clippings, 1950s (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Communism and Labor, 1954-1960 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Communism: Teaching about, 1964-1965 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Communist Party and the "Jewish Question", 1966 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Communist Party: Fronts & Splinters, 1955-1968 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Communist Party: New Line, 1954-1964 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Communist Party: Outlawing of, 1954-1965 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Community Council: Agency Relationships & Agreements, 1957, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Community Press Service, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Community Relations: Materials, 1940s-1950s (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Confederate Flag, 1952, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Congress of Freedom, 1956, 1961-1962 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Congress of Industrial Organizations, 1954 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Congress on Racial Equality, 1940s-1960s (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Congress on Racial Equality: Boston, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Congressional Investigations: Reform of, 1954 (Box 7, Folder 14a)
  - Conservative Parties, 1962-1966 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Constitutional Rights: Hennings Sub-Committee, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 15a)
  - Construction Trade and Minorities, 1960s-1970s (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Consumers: Exploitation of Poor Communities, 1966-1967 (Box 7, Folder 16a)
  - Consumers: New York Consumers Assembly (2nd), Jan 13, 1968 (Box MSOS006, Folder 1)
  - Consumer Protection, 1963-1971 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Conte, Silvio, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Contract Compliance: Boston, 1968-1970 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Cooperatives, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence: General, 1954-1958 (Box 7, Folder 20a)
  - Correspondence: General, 1968-1969 (Box 7, Folder 20b)
  - Correspondence: General, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 20c)
  - Correspondence: General, 1971-1977 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Coughlin. Father Charles, 1936, 1955, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Counter Attack, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Countercurrent, 1939 (Box 7, Folder 22a)
  - Criminal Case Reform, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Crisis-in-Jobs Project: New England, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 23a)
  - Cuba, 1961-1963 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Cushing Awards, undated (Box 7, Folder 24a)
  - Debs Foundation, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Defensive League of Registered Americans, Inc., 1962 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Demonstrations (Non-Violent Techniques): Talk by Julius Bernstein, undated (Box 7, Folder 27a)
  - Detroit: Jewish Labor Committee, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 27b)
  - Dialogues Boston, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Disarmament, 1960-1963 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Discrimination: General, 1960-1964 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Discrimination: Social Clubs, undated, 1947-1955 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Displaced Persons, undated, 1947-1950 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Dissenting Democrats, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Douglas, Charles B., 1958-1963 (Box 7A, Folder 1)
  - Draft Law, 1966, 1967 (Box 7A, Folder 2)
  - Draft Resistance, 1968 (Box 7A, Folder 3)
  - Dresser, Robert B., 1961 (Box 7A, Folder 4)
  - Drinan, Robert, 1971 (Box 7A, Folder 5)
  - Dukakis, Michael, 1976 (Box 7A, Folder 6)
  - Economy: General, 1975 (Box 7A, Folder 6)
  - Education: General, 1960s-1970s (Box 7A, Folder 7)
  - Education: General, 1975 (Box 7A, Folder 8)
  - Education: Labor's Views on, 1974 (Box 7A, Folder 9)
  - Education: Massachusetts Conference, 1955-1956 (Box 7A, Folder 10)
  - Educational Television, 1950s (Box 7A, Folder 11)
  - Eichmann Trial, 1960-1961 (Box 7A, Folder 12)
  - Election, 1976 (Box 7A, Folder 13)
  - Elections: Referenda, 1976 (Box 7A, Folder 14)
  - Electoral College, 1969-1977 (Box 7A, Folder 15)
  - Employment, 1970, 1974, 1977 (Box 7A, Folder 16)
  - Employment: Affirmative Action, 1972-1976 (Box 7A, Folder 17)
  - Employment: Boston, 1960s-1980s (Box 7A, Folder 18)
  - Employment: Discrimination, undated, 1949, 1951-1958 (Box 7A, Folder 19)
  - Employment: Discrimination, 1959-1962 (Box 7A, Folder 20)
  - Employment: Discrimination, 1963-1969 (Box 7A, Folder 21)
  - Employment: Discrimination, 1970-1973 (Box 7A, Folder 22)
  - Employment: Discrimination (Boston), 1961-1963 (Box 7A, Folder 23)
  - Employment: Discrimination (Boston), 1965-1975 (Box 7A, Folder 24)
  - Employment: Discrimination: Building Trades, 1961-1966, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Employment: Discrimination: International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Employment: Discrimination, Jewish, 1953-1968 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Employment: Discrimination: Massachusetts, 1947, 1953-1968 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Employment: Discrimination: Massachusetts Civil Service, 1963-1966 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Employment: Discrimination: Massachusetts Civil Service, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Employment: Discrimination: Plumbers Union, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Employment: Discrimination: State Employees, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Employment: General, 1974-1977 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Employment: Seniority vs. Minority Preference, 1974-1976 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Energy Crisis, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Energy: Off-Shore, 1975-1977 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Engagement Calendars, 1974, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Episcopal Society for Cultural and Radical Unity, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Ethical Society of Boston, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity Commission, 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Equal Rights Amendment, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Executive Board, Transport Workers Union of America, 1938, 1939 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Facts Forum, 1954-1955 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Fair Educational Practices Legislation, 1949-1956 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Fair Employment Practice Commission, 1945-1964 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Family Service Association, 1973-1975 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Family Service Association of Greater Boston: Social Advisory Committee, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Farah Boycott, 1972, 1974-1977 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Farm Labor, 1960-1965 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Farm Labor, 1966-1970 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Farm Workers, 1973-1974, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - FBI & Civil Rights, undated, 1952-1954, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Feeney, Father Leonard, 1952-1974 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Feminism/Women's Rights Movement, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 6a)
  - Filibuster Rules, 1954-1964 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Film, 1949-1958 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Fluoridation, 1961-1964 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Food Stamps, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - For America, 1956-1957 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Foundations: Investigation of, 1954-1956, 1960, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Frank, Barney, undated (Box 9, Folder 12a)
  - Fraternal Bookshop, NYC, undated (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Frederick Douglass Bookstore, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Freedom Bookshelf, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Freedom Budget (A. Philip Randolph Institute), 1966 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Freedom Budget (A. Philip Randolph Institute), 1967-1969 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Freedom Riders, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Freedom Riders: Reverse (Cape Cod), 1962 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Freedom Schools (Colorado Springs), 1964-1965 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Free Society/Association, 1965-1966 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Full Employment Week, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Fund for the Republic, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 22a)
  - Genesis 2 (Harvard University), 1973 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Genocide Treaties, 1953-1966 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Genocide Treaties, 1968, 1970-1976 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Germany, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Germany: De-Nazification, 1949-1963 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - God & Country Rally, 1963-1969 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Goldwater, Barry, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Governor's Conference on Civil Rights, 1958, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Grape Boycott, 1967-1970 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Grape Boycott, 1971-1976 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Greater Boston Labor Council, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Green Mountain Patriots, 1963, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Green Mountain Rifleman, 1953-1956 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Guaranteed Annual Wage, 1953-1954, 1966-1971 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Hall, Gordon, 1951-1966 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Hammer & Steel Newsletter, 1962-1968 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Harrington, Michael, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Harvard: "Labor in Politics" Series, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Harvard: National Priorities Conference, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Hate Mail, 1955-1958 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Haymarket People's Fund, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Health Care, 1976-1977 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Health Insurance, 1959-1961, 1964-1965, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Health Insurance, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Health Insurance and Medicaid, 1963-1973 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Health Insurance: National, 1970-1975 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Herald of Freedom, 1963-1967 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Higher Education: Discrimination Quotas, 1948-1957 (Box 10, Folder 13a)
  - Hill, Herbert, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 13b)
  - Hispanic Community: Boston, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 13c)
  - Hood, Otis (Case), 1954 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Hospital Workers & J.L.C., 1966-1967, 1972-1976 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - House Un-American Activities Committee, 1958-1964 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - HUAC and Women Strike for Peace, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Housing, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 17a)
  - Housing: Anti-Integration Violence, 1953-1954, 1959, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Housing: Boston, 1963-1967 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Housing: Boston, 1970-1972, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Housing: Boston Conference, 1963-1966 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Housing: Boston University Law school Report I (pp. 1-125), 1968 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Housing: Boston University Law school Report II (pp.126-finish), 1968 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Housing: Discrimination, 1950-1970 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Housing: Discrimination (Brochures & Pamphlets), 1950-1970 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Housing: Elderly, 1954-1973 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Housing: Executive Order, 1962-1963 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Housing: Executive Order: HUD Tenant Policy Council Suits, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Housing: Legislation (Mass.), 1968-1974 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Housing Maintenance Laborers, Local 367, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Housing: Massachusetts, 1964-1970 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Housing: Model Cities Program, 1966-1967 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Housing: New York, 1950, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Housing: Off-Base, 1966-1967 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Housing: Organization for Social and Technical Innovation Manual I (pp. 1-146), 1969 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Housing: Organization for Social and Technical Innovation Manual II (pp. 147-end), 1969 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Human Events, 1960-1961, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Human Rights, undated (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Human Rights Directory (Boston), 1970 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Human Rights: Genocide Convention, 1950-1968 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Humphrey Hawkins Bill, 1975-1977 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Hungary, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Immigration, 1952-1955 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Immigration, 1956-1957 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Immigration, 1958-1961 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Immigration: Corsi Case, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Immigration: McCarran Act, 1951-1953 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Independence Foundation, The, 1958 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Indian Land Claims, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Indian Rights, 1952, 1969-1977 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Indian Tribes, 1973-1976 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Indignation Convention, 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Industrial Workers of the World, undated (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Institutes/Conferences (Labor; Civil Rights; Civil Liberties), 1940s (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Institutes/Conferences (Labor; Civil Rights; Civil Liberties), 1950s (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Institutes/Conferences (Labor; Civil Rights; Civil Liberties), 1960s (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Institutes/Conferences (Labor; Civil Rights; Civil Liberties): Clippings, 1950s-1960s (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Institute for American Democracy, 1967-1968 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Intercultural/Education, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1955-1962 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 42: Charge of Anti-Semitism, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - International Labor Organization (ILO), 1955-1957 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - International Ladies Garment Workers Union, 1960-1963 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - ILGWU vs. the NAACP, 1961-1963 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - International Rescue and Relief Committee, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - International Rescue and Relief Committee, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, 1953, 1955-1959 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Israel, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Israel, 1974-1977 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Israel: Black Support, undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Israel: Mapam Expulsions, 1951, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Israel: US Labor Support, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Israel: US Labor Support, 1974-1977 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Jewish Advocate: 75th Anniversary, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 7a)
  - Jewish Community Council, 1947-1958 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Jewish Community Council, 1965-1967 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Jewish Community Council, 1968-1970 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Jewish Community Council, 1971-1975 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Jewish Community Council: Defamation & Violence, 1954-1958, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Jewish Community Council: Job Opportunity Committees, 1953, 1955-1956 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Jewish Community Council: Metropolitan Boston, 1959-1977 (Box 12, Folder 13a)
  - Jewish Community Council: Minutes, 1970-1972 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Jewish Community Council: Security for Inner City Jews, 1960, 1968, 1970-1973 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Jewish Daily Forward, 1976-1977 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Jewish Defense League, 1969-1971 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Jewish Holiday Observance, 1950s-1970s (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Jewish Labor Bund: "The Other Way", 1971 (Box 12, Folder 18a)
  - Jewish Labor Committee, undated (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Jewish Labor Committee, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Jewish Labor Committee, 1945 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Jewish Labor Committee, Jan 1946-Apr 1946 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Jewish Labor Committee, May 1946-Jun 1946 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Jewish Labor Committee, Jul 1946-Sep 1946 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Jewish Labor Committee, Oct 1946-Dec 1946 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Jewish Labor Committee, Jan 1947-Jun 1947 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Jewish Labor Committee, Jul 1947-Dec 1947 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Jewish Labor Committee, 1948 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Jewish Labor Committee, 1949 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Jewish Labor Committee, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Jewish Labor Committee, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Jewish Labor Committee, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Jewish Labor Committee, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Jewish Labor Committee, 1954 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Jewish Labor Committee, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Jewish Labor Committee, 1956 I (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Jewish Labor Committee, 1956 II (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Jewish Labor Committee, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Jewish Labor Committee, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Jewish Labor Committee, 1959 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Jewish Labor Committee, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Jewish Labor Committee, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Jewish Labor Committee, Jan 1962-May 1962 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Jewish Labor Committee, Jun 1962-Dec 1962 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Jewish Labor Committee, Jan 1963-May 1963 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Jewish Labor Committee, Jun 1963-Dec 1963 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Jewish Labor Committee, Jan 1964-Jun 1964 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Jewish Labor Committee, Jul 1964-Dec 1964 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Jewish Labor Committee, Jan 1965-Apr 1965 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Jewish Labor Committee, May 1965-Aug 1965 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Jewish Labor Committee, Sep 1965-Dec 1965 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Jewish Labor Committee, Jan 1966-Apr 1966 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Jewish Labor Committee, May 1966-Jul 1966 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Jewish Labor Committee, Jan 1967-Apr 1967 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Jewish Labor Committee, May 1967-Dec 1967 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Jewish Labor Committee, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Jewish Labor Committee, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Jewish Labor Committee, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Jewish Labor Committee, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Jewish Labor Committee, 1966-1972 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Jewish Labor Committee, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Jewish Labor Committee, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Jewish Labor Committee, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Jewish Labor Committee, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Jewish Labor Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Jewish Labor Committee (JLC): Boston Conference, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - JLC: Boston Newsletter, 1955, 1960-1963 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - JLC: Boston Newsletter, 1964-1966 (Box 15, Folder 11)